Sailing!
Stronger than ever!
Here it comes! What's that? A shark?
Whoa! It's so close!
What's this?
There's something in here!
Is it big?
Yes!
Good morning!
Good morning.
This background means,
It's time for the Sea Fishing Yuru and Meepan Channel.
This is the second installment.
Today we are at a place called Kashima Port in Ibaraki Prefecture.
What a surprise, we thought we would proceed with just two people today, but another person came.
Yay!
Here we go!
Hello.
Please introduce yourself.
I am Mizuki Hiraoka, a 4th year student. Pleased to meet you.
I'm Michi.
Why did you come to us, Micchan?
Actually, my father is a fisherman,
Father!
He's like a helper.
He's a very nice helper.
Really? Thank you very much.
I saw the last one and it looked like too much fun,
I said I wanted to go.
I was really looking forward to it.
Today, I'm going to..,
I'm going to catch a flounder.
Yay!
It's a high-class fish. I love flounder.
What do you think? Have you ever caught a flounder?
No, I haven't.
Maybe not even nymphs.
Flounder is at the bottom?
In? Do they sleep?
I have an image of them in the sand.
It's crazy. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm off.
Let's go!
Do you miss it?
I miss it so much.
When I was quite little,
My dad's boat came home,
Cleaning?
You cleaned it? I would do it,
I found a squid in the corner of the boat,
I was playing with it,
I was playing with it.
That's so cute.
I miss it so much.
The flounder is still down there, though,
But you don't give up immediately after you get hit by a bull,
It's not like they give up right after they get hit,
It takes a while,
It bites,
After it bites into the inside,
After it's all eaten,
If you don't give it up, you won't catch it.
They say they run away.
That's why they are often a bit eaten.
The bait.
The bait fish.
What is the bait for flounder?
I saw sardines.
Live sardines?
You mean you put live sardines on them?
Just one hook,
Over here on the nose,
Over here, on the back,
Why?
They say it's enough to catch one fish today.
One fish?
Today, it's only good to catch one fish.
It's a little hard to catch.
Is everyone OK?
When you're ready,
Let's get started.
Let's do it.
Okay, please.
Yes, please.
Okay.
Have a good day.
I'm pulling. It's already started.
Wow!
Oh, but I don't know.
I don't know.
How deep is it?
Can you see it?
Let's get it up on the top here.
Sparkle.
That's amazing.
That's fast.
That's good.
That's great!
Take me with you.
Fast!
That's great.
I'll let you out for a minute.
Oh, my gosh!
How big is this thing?
Oh, Came!
I'm so happy!
My hand is about this big.
Congratulations on your first flathead!
Anyone can catch a flathead, but you're fast!
I was in elementary school, or just before I turned 10.
You fished? I don't remember it like this.
I was thinking of catching a tiny piece of fish... and I was doing a little taste fishing.
I was fishing.
I thought something was coming...
It's here!
Oh, it's pulling me in!
Yes!
It's so heavy!
Oh, it's so heavy!
It's stuck!
Oh, but I'm here!
Oh, yeah!
Oh!
A second one!
Looks like it's bigger than the first one.
Yeah, about two and a half.
It's definitely bigger.
Oh, I want to catch one! I want to catch one!
That's an enticement.
Let's do it again.
Slowly lowering the gap.
Not quite there yet.
I need you to pull.
Pull, pull, pull!
Come on.
Not eating?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I want to catch it.
Just one fish.
I just want to catch one.
I just got one.
Hold on a little longer.
Come on, bite me.
Yes, sir.
But don't...
Don't point it at me, please.
It's heavy. It's heavy.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
I caught another keeper.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
How did you do that?
Third one!
Flounder. What do you think?
About the same as the first, second, and third? Probably the same size.
Is it getting bigger?
It's a little bit light.
Is it heavy?
I think it's here.
I hope it's here.
I hope there's something on it.
There's something in here!
Is it big?
It's a sunfish!
Wow! It's the sun!
Congratulations!
I caught it! I'm so happy!
We did it!
I caught it, finally!
I got it!
I'm so happy! The first one.
Pattadaaan!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy!
Thank you, Mr. Flounder!
Now I can tell my dad I caught it!
I feel a little
It's nice.
Is that the floor, right there?
Oh, you hit it.
Yes, there it is. Here it comes! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, it's got marks on it.
It's strong, too.
He's here.
Still here? Shark?
It's done.
What's this?
What is it? This.
Sea bass?
Oh, my God.
Here comes the sea bass.
Sea bass?
It's huge!
Got sea bass!
I'm scared.
Give it to him once.
Yes, sir.
Please take the sea bass.
I'm the only one who hasn't caught one yet
I've changed places a bit
Let's see if we can catch it here.
Let's try our luck.
I'd like to catch one.
I'll be satisfied if I catch one.
A lot.
But even if I don't catch one, it's still a lot of fun.
It's fun.
I'm sorry, I'm going to have to move now.
Okay.
I'll move a little.
Please try it. Move.
Okay.
Okay, that's it, everybody.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Okay.
So we're back. Here's the land.
And here is what I caught today.
Let's see if it shows up on the screen.
The flounder that Micchan caught... it's turned over.
That's Mr. Suzuki and the flounder Miban caught.
I didn't get anything.
I did, but I knew... that's where it started.
You can't catch a fish without a hook.
I was frustrated.
It's frustrating, isn't it?
But now I have caught so many fish, I'd like to start cooking.
Today I'll make sashimi and carpaccio.
I'll do my best.
First, we'll remove the head.
We can't do anything, so we'll just watch.
We'll do our best. We'll just watch.
We'll just watch.
Wow, but you got it clean.
You did a great job.
It's amazing, but it's so beautiful.
That's great.
Okay, we got a quarter of the way down.
It's so beautiful, there's not even a little bit left.
Thank you very much.
Not too good.
It's just a little bit more.
That's great, isn't it?
There you go.
Thank you.
You did it.
That's great.
I think we'll be making a lot of sashimi and carpaccio.
The meat is amazing.
It's so hard!
Sashimi is ready!
Yes, sir.
Next, sashimi of flatfish.
What are you going to do?
This...
If I did it alone, I'd be picking it off.
I'm sure I would.
Yes, I would.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. - Yes.
One more and we're good.
I'm good.
It's so cute.
So stylish.
Stylish.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
That's great.
Thank you.
Looks delicious
Oh, man.
Now it's done!
This is flatfish sashimi.
Carpaccio!
Suzuki's sashimi
Shall we have some then?
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit!
First of all...
Today's main dish.
I shook it, and everyone loved it.
Mr. Mirei caught it.
It's a flounder.
A big flounder.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Looks delicious.
Nice and juicy.
Thank you for catching that.
That way.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Two.
Bon appétit. I went for two.
Mmm.
Puripuripuri! Mmmm!
The elasticity is really amazing.
Freshly caught. Delicious!
Then carpaccio, too? Yes, please.
Bon appétit. Bon appétit.
Carpaccio. Carpaccio.
Carpaccio.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
Yum. Yum.
Yum. Yum. Yum.
Delicious.
Delicious
Another dish
That's great.
But I'm happy for you... because you caught your target today, the flounder.
You caught a lot of flounder... four.
Yeah, we caught a lot.
Do you have a goal for the next time you want to catch something?
I told you earlier...
You love yellowtail.
I see.
I also like yellowtail very much.
I love yellowtail so much!
Is it only caught on the Sea of Japan side?
Is that so?
There's a lot of yellowtail in my hometown right now.
I have to go there.
That's possible.
That's true.
Your father is a fisherman on the Sea of Japan side.
We'll go together.
I'll ask him to teach me.
I'd like you to continue.
I'd like to go to yellowtail.
If you ever get the chance...
I'd like you to tell Micchan's father
By all means.
I can't.
It's a dream come true.
I'm looking forward to it.
Then I hope we can do something, so please
Thank you for watching this video.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe and like my channel.
Bye bye.
See you soon.